const questions = [
    {
    question: 'Which was the last nation to win the FIFA World Cup as the host?',
    choice1: 'France',
    choice2: 'Brazil',
    choice3: 'Germany',
    choice4: 'Italy',
    answer: 1,
    extra: 'France won the World Cup as the host in 1998'
    },
    {
    question: 'Who is the highest goal scorer in the history of the FIFA World Cup?',
    choice1: 'Gerd Muller',
    choice2: 'Pele',
    choice3: 'Miroslav Klose',
    choice4: 'Ronaldo Nazario',
    answer: 3,
    extra: 'Miroslav Klose scored 16 goals between 2002 and 2014'   
    },
    {
    question: 'Which country has won the most FIFA World Cups?',
    choice1: 'Germany',
    choice2: 'Brazil',
    choice3: 'Italy',
    choice4: 'England',
    answer: 2,
    extra: 'Brazil have won 5 tournaments. 1958, 1962, 1970, 1994 and 2002'    
    },
    {
    question: 'Which country have never qualified for the FIFA World Cup?',
    choice1: 'North Korea',
    choice2: 'Cuba',
    choice3: 'Venezuela',
    choice4: 'Haiti',
    answer: 3,   
    extra: 'Cuba went in 1938, Haiti in 1974 and North Korea 1966 and 2010'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which country has the most World Cup losses?',
    choice1: 'Serbia',
    choice2: 'Germany',
    choice3: 'Mexico',
    choice4: 'England',
    answer: 3,   
    extra: 'Mexico has lost 27 out of 57 games in the World Cup'
    },
    {
    question: 'How old was the oldest player to ever play in the FIFA World Cup?',
    choice1: '39',
    choice2: '47',
    choice3: '42',
    choice4: '45',
    answer: 4,   
    extra: 'Essam El-Hadary from Egypt play in 2018 with 45 years and 161 days old'
    },
    {
    question: 'How old was the youngest player to ever play in the FIFA World Cup?',
    choice1: '17',
    choice2: '19',
    choice3: '18',
    choice4: '16',
    answer: 1,
    extra: 'Norman Whiteside with 17 years and 40 days old debuted in 1982'   
    },
    {
    question: 'How fast was the fastest ever FIFA World Cup goal?',
    choice1: '18.3 seconds',
    choice2: '24.2 seconds',
    choice3: '8.2 seconds',
    choice4: '10.8 seconds',
    answer: 4,   
    extra: 'From Turkey, Hakan Sukur scored against South Korea in 2002'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which country has the most World Cup wins?',
    choice1: 'Brazil',
    choice2: 'Italy',
    choice3: 'Germany',
    choice4: 'Argentina',
    answer: 1,   
    extra: 'Brazil have won 73 out of 109 games played in the World Cup'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which country have been eliminated in the first round the most times?',
    choice1: 'USA',
    choice2: 'Cameroon',
    choice3: 'Scotland',
    choice4: 'Mexico',
    answer: 3,   
    extra: 'Scotland have been eliminated 8 out of 8 times in the first round'
    },
    {
    question: 'Where was the very first World Cup held?',
    choice1: 'England',
    choice2: 'Brazil',
    choice3: 'Uruguay',
    choice4: 'Italy',
    answer: 3,   
    extra: 'In 1930, Uruguay held the first World Cup'
    },
    {
    question: 'How often is the FIFA World Cup?',
    choice1: '3 years',
    choice2: '5 years',
    choice3: '4 years',
    choice4: '2 years',
    answer: 3,   
    extra: '4 years gap allows time for the qualification fixtures'
    },
    {
    question: 'When was the first World Cup held?',
    choice1: '1930',
    choice2: '1920',
    choice3: '1950',
    choice4: '1940',
    answer: 1,   
    extra: 'Uruguay held the first World Cup in 1930'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which country hosted the World Cup in 2018?',
    choice1: 'Belgium',
    choice2: 'Russia',
    choice3: 'France',
    choice4: 'Croatia',
    answer: 2,   
    extra: 'Russia was selected to host the 2018 World Cup back in 2010'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which country will host the World Cup in 2022?',
    choice1: 'Kuwait',
    choice2: 'USA',
    choice3: 'Qatar',
    choice4: 'Mexico',
    answer: 3,   
    extra: 'Qatar was selected to host the 2022 World Cup back in 2010'
    },
    {
    question: 'How many teams participate in the tournament phase?',
    choice1: '24 teams',
    choice2: '16 teams',
    choice3: '28 teams',
    choice4: '32 teams',
    answer: 4,   
    extra: 'The tournament was expanded to 32 teams in 1998'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which is the only team that played in every tournament?',
    choice1: 'Brazil',
    choice2: 'Germany',
    choice3: 'Italy',
    choice4: 'Argentina',
    answer: 1,   
    extra: 'Brazil has participated in all 21 World Cups'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which team have the nickname "Azzurri"?',
    choice1: 'Italy',
    choice2: 'France',
    choice3: 'Uruguay',
    choice4: 'Argentina',
    answer: 1,   
    extra: 'Traditional Savoy Blue, Italy is know as the "Azzurri'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which team have the nickname "Three Lions"?',
    choice1: 'Spain',
    choice2: 'Netherlands',
    choice3: 'England',
    choice4: 'Sri Lanka',
    answer: 3,   
    extra: 'England use Three Lions in their uniform since 1872'
    },
    {
    question: 'Which team have the nickname "The Red Fury"?',
    choice1: 'Chile',
    choice2: 'Portugal',
    choice3: 'China',
    choice4: 'Spain',
    answer: 4,   
    extra: 'Spain is "The Red Fury" for the strong and physical way of playing'
    },
];